Guide to the Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Tom Davis papers, 1994-2008
  - Y2K and DC, June 17, 1998 and March 2, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Rural buildout, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Transmission speed, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Performance metrics, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Broadband, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Hi-Tech scorecards, 2000-2002 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Equal access, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Positions on Broadband, 1999, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Broadband reports / studies, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Broadband reports / studies, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Satellite Radio, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Spectrum management, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Internet hunting, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Must carry (multicast), 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Satellite Radio, September 2002 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - DTV Transition, July 22, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Telecom rewrite, 2004-2005 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission) Speed Access, July 2004, November 2006 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - GAO (Government Accountability Office) Special Access, October-November 2006 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Special Access, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Telecom, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Metro briefing book, March 2007 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Issues binder with stances, 31 issues Abortion to Welfare, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Town Hall meetings (issue binder Abortion to Veterans Affairs), January-February 2004 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - League of Women Voters Speech (talking points), January 20, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Town meetings issue binder. (Western Prince William), Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Town hall meetings issue binder, March 4, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - (Tom Davis sticker on cover) Town hall meetings issue binder, March 4-6, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Issue binder, Amnesty / Flake Bill to Welfare, Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Issue binder, Amnesty / Flake Bill to Welfare, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Farm Bill, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Transparencies of multiple issues, Undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 2015 report (budget for FY 1998), June 24, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Slots / Perimeter (Reagan National Airport) information, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Deborah Katz Pueschel FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) file, February-March 1999 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Dumfries sound walls, March 9, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - VRE (Virginia Railway Express information, February 19, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Eye-Gaze, LC Technologies, 1997-1999 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Transportation and infrastructure organizational information, December 1998 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Safety belts on school buses. (CRS report), January 9, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - OMC (Office of Motor Carrier)info, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - General transportation articles, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Sample talking points (Healthcare), October 10, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Forum invites and info, January-February 1999 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - MCW (?) recommendations, September 23-24, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Competition in airline industry, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - National Park overflight issues, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Frank Wolf, Dulles Corridor HOV lanes, November 9, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - HOV 66 issues, July 16, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l (National) Capital Region, Congestion and Mobility summit, August-September 1998 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Ferry information, October 26-27, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Vienna / Maple Ave TEA-21, December 1998 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - City of Fairfax, road improvements, November 1998 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Prince William transportation Study, December 2, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Doceit(?) OST, 1998, unfair exclusionary practices (Department of Transportation) (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - ICT (International Computers & Telecommunications)information, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Potomac Tracon (FAA (Federal Aviation Administration)), February 23, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - McCain's Objections to omnibus and budget reforms, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Ongoing Chip N. Project, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) Reauthorization, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Airbag info, August 1998 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - CSX: Annie Havens STB (Surface Transportation Board) info, September-October 1998 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Graduated Driver's License info, September 30, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - T & I (Transportation and Infrastructure) mark-up materials, July 23, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - SUV information, July 1998 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - T & I (Transportation and Infrastructure) Appropriations Committee concerns, September 2-4, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Transportation letters, May-July 1998 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - MCW (?)Appropriations requests, September 11-14, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Harbor Service User Fee, December 1998 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - GW (George Washington University)/ NTSB (National Transportation Safety Board) Dear Colleague, January 1999 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - AIP (Airport Improvement Program) Articles, October 1998 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - PTO (Patent and Trademark Office) info, November 1998 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Public buildings, H.R. 4034 Hearing, October 2, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - New Hope Project on Glen Carlyn Road, September 9, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Transportation Trust Fund (CRS report), February 24, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Public Buildings subcommittee, mark-up, September 14, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - TEA-21 funding, July 1998 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Occuquan, Rt. 123 Bridge expansion, January 8, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - T & I (Transportation and Infrastructure) Y2K hearings, September 23-28, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) Y2K info, August 1998 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Aviation subcommittee H.R. 3741, safe skies initiative, Rodney Slater testimony, July 30, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Perimeter rule information, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Hare Krishna Law, October 1998 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Travel Agents Community, Aviations Subcommittee, September 10, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - H.R. 1846, Aviation subcommittee hearing, July-August 1998 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - FAA (Federal Aviation Administration) Reauthorization Conference Request, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Kapton wiring (on planes), 1998 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - H.R. 2456, September 1997 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - H.R. 3734, April-May 1998 (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Info and old letters on corporate welfare, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - White House person reform info on plan, June 4, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Life insurance annuity info, February 1998 (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Tax treatment of employer-offered parking benefits, January 1999 (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - Y2K tax info, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - John Faber information, Petroleum insurance moratorium, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - Kerosene information, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - Youth Gang Violence Summit, April 20, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - Air and Space Museum, September-October 1996 (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous: Transportation; taxes, 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - Dulles Airport, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - The Western Transportation Corridor, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 68)
  - SOV (Single Occupancy Vehicle) access on the I-95/395/495 Interchange, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - 123 widening, February-March 1995 (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - OECD (Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development) shipbuilding, July 14, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - Ringling Bros, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - Dolphins, February 1997 (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - Clean Air, 1995, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - OSHA (Occupational Safety and Health Administration), Undated (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - NRDC (Natural Resources Defense Council) briefing paper, Stealth Attack (Environmental protection), July 1995 (Box 45, Folder 76)
  - 1st Session Interns, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 77)
  - FOT's with incomplete info or have not shown up, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 78)
  - High School mid session interns, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 79)
  - 2nd session interns, April 1998 (Box 45, Folder 80)
  - CBE (Cost-Benefit-Effectiveness) user's guide. Karl Seiler Associates, Reston, VA, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Superfund, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Thank you, H.R. 961, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Retirement plan operated by D.C., March 1995 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - FY98 Defense requests, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Federal buildings; Dod (Department of Defense) in NoVA (Northern Virginia), 1997 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - USAIR John/Tom. (invoices and supply forms from Intelligent Solutions Benchmark Systems; raw data from Campaign-Tel), 1995 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Wetlands, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Chief of Police John Skinner (not foldered), January 1995 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Congressional mail and memos, 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Mining, October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Timber salvage amendment, February, April 1996 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - CRS (Congressional Research Services) memo regarding Congress confirming appointment made by the D.C. Mayor, July 22, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - CFC (chlorofluorocarbons), ozone, October 12-16, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Bear Protection Act, H.R. 2240, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Timber, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Briefing materials: Forest Service Issues, American Forest & Paper Association, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Animal Research DoD (Department of Defense), December 8, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Environment, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Animal protection, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Lake Fairfax theme park, April 25, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 260 National Parks, September-October 1995 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - H.R. 1745 Utah Parks, September 1995 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - National Parks H.R. 1091, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - U.S. and Japan: Open Skies equals Free Trade, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Testimony and statements regarding the Woodrow Wilson Bridge, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Modular Design System (MDS), April 1997 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Rules of the House of Representatives, January 7, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - National Economic Crossroads Transportation Efficiency Act of 1997, March 1997 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Davis office computer, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Subcommittee on Aviation hearing, June 11, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Reston bus system, October 1996 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - 11 Miscellaneous H.R. reports from the 104th and 105th congress, March 1995-June 1997 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Committee on Government Reform and Oversight regarding Y2K, February-March 1997 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Government Reform and Oversight regarding Y2K (dark blue folder), February-March 1997 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - H.R. 2086, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Y2K (dark blue folder), February-March 1997 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Government reform mark-up (H.R. 2086), April 24, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Subcommittee on Human Resources testimony; Public employee retirement; Next Week In Congress, April 26, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Downsizing and minimum wage, May 1996 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - American Society for Industrial Security, April 1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Travelgate, May 1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Travelgate, July 1993, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Government Shutdown Prevention Act, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous: Public buildings GSA; commuting; Y2K; OPM (Office of Personnel Management) privatization; other acts, April-July 1996 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Oversight of Federal Information Policy, June 1996 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Y2K, September 15, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Government reform: GMIT (Government Management, Information and Technology) subcommittee hearing, April 25, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Government Committee: 2000 Census Hearing, 2954, March-June 1996 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - GAOPA (Government Accountability Office Personnel Appeals Board) Willis, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Budget FY95 Statistics, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Davis Biography, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Articles on Davis (not foldered), 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - 1993 Budget main, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Country vs. National statistics and comparisons, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Davis speeches and articles, 1992-1994 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - County facts and statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Davis articles, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Media List, October 12, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax Budget FY 1993; School budget (Fairfax Board of Supervisors), 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Student loans. (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Student loans. (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - National Education Association and tax-exempt status, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Role models America, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Thank you's (to Kris (Hathaway)) (Thank you letters from children and schools), 1997 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Letters of thanks and support (ED), 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Literacy programs, 1991-1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Smokey the Bear, September-October 1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Title IX, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Americorps, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Classroom, January 22, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Ebonics, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Adult education (CRS reports), 1994, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Employment, Training, and Literacy Enhancement Act. H.R. 1385, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - The Globe Program in Virginia, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - National Science Foundation. (CRS report), May 1995 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - School Construction Initiative, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - The Lightspan Partnership, Inc, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - We the People, Center for Civic Education, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Computers in education, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Tilghman Prep School / Rev. Saddler, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - National / Virginia reading association and National Writing Project, 1995, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - National Diffusion Network, February-March 1995 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Prosoft, IT and Learning, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - FCPS (Fairfax County Public Schools): PTA (Parent-Teacher Association): Minority student achievement, April 1997 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Campus Gag Rule, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - H.E.L.P. (Helping Empower Low-Income Parents) Scholarship, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - National Testing / Education standards, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Reading Excellence Act, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Partnership for Technology Education, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Education Funding, September 28, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - National Education Association, 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Religious amendment, H.J.R. 184, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - American Community Act, July 1996 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - NEA (National Education Association), 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - American Association of University Women, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Religion in schools, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - TV violence / ratings, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Family rights. (CRS report), March 31, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - American University of the Caribbean, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 1-2, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, October-December 1998 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, November 24, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, October-November 1998 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525 (not foldered), October-December 1998 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 9, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 8-9, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 3-8, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 3, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Constituent mail with response regarding President Clinton, H.R. 525, December 2-3, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Northern Virginia BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) working group report, December 1, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Arlington County proposal to the Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC) Commission, July 7, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) briefing binder, July 2005 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), August 10, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), July-August 2005 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - (BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) Military bases GAO (Government Accountability Office) report, July 2005 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Public information meeting for the EIS (Environmental Impact Statement) for BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), January 24, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) report to the President, volume 1, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) report to the President, volume 2, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Fort Belvoir GROC (Committee on Government Reform and Oversight) Field Hearing, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Clo's BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) binder (1 of 2), July 2005 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Clo's BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) binder (2 of 2), July 2005 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) report, volume 3 (Army) (1 of 2), May 2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) report, volume 3 (Army) (2 of 2), May 2005 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), 2005 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Post BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure) implementation (includes CDs on night vision equipment), 2005 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Finance, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Articles and clippings (re campaign finance), 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Belvoir Transportation, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Drugs, October 15, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - National Drug Intelligence Center, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - TPA (Trade Promotion Authority) (Bipartisan Trade Promotion Authority Act of 2001) (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Election reform, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - The case for baseball in Virginia, Circa 1999-2001 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - VBSA (Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority), 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - DIC (Dependency and Indemnity Compensation) / Veterans, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - No Child Left Behind, January 23, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - School Choice, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 1, No Child Left Behind, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 1, No Child Left Behind implementation kit, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Ethnic outreach contacts, 2000-2004 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Meeting with Hon. Tom Davis United States Congress (Puerto Rico), February 16, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Puerto Rico: President's Task Force on PR's status, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Gold Star Wives, Edie Smith, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Taiwan FTA (Federal Trade Administration), 2006 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Korea Visa Waiver Program, Carrie Bring, October 2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Luis Perez (Luis Fortuno friend), 2006 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Cuba embassy, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Ly Tong (Vietnam), 2006 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Falun Gong (organ) harvesting issue, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Vietnam human trafficking, Jackie bong Wright, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - El Salvador Bill (Hilda Solis), Eleonor Velazquez, July 2005 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - USAFA: religious guidelines, Major Damon Menendez, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - China torture (Mr. Tong Qimiao), Larry Pratt, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Sudan. H.R. 723, March 6, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Filipino Refugees, Ur Jaddou (Vietnam Caucus), December 2005 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Eritrea-Ethiopia conflict and peace progress, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Immigration OG (?), 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - IT's Academic Day, Sophie Altman, HRES 471, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Korea Free Trade Agreement, Andy Olsen, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - FY06 Defense Authorization, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Korea Day Bill, Harold Pyon, HRES 487, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Boy Scout Amicus brief, Robert Bork, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - FY06 Budget reconciliation, October-November 2005 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - National Military Appreciation Month, H.Con.Res. 328 108th Congress, April 2005 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Asian / Pacific Heritage Resolution, Michael Layman, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Foreign Policy: Henry Hyde United Nations Reform Bill H.R. 2745, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Foreign Policy: Abuse of detainees at GITMO (Guantanamo Bay), June 2005 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - H.R. 4277 Premium Pay Conversion, May-June 2000 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Sale of U.S. ports to Dubai, February-March 2006 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Lobbying reform, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Constituents of Concern, February 6, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - FY06 Defense Authorization, May 11, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - DARPA (Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency), 2005 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Egypt terror attacks resolution, H.R. 795, May 2006 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - American Business Council of the Gulf Countries, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - DSS discontinuing processing security clearances, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Deaths in Iraq, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Taiwan high level visits, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Briefing to Virginia Congressional Delegation, June 26, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Landmine treaty ban (Ottawa), October 16, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Prepo Equipment Program (PEP), Bernard Bickham, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Davis / McCain amendment, Vietnamese, 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam: 30th anniversary of Fall of Saigon, 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Israel Caucus, May 3, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - USCIS (U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services) GROC (Committee on Government Reform and Oversight) Case, 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Indians, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Voter Confidence Act H.R. 550, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - BRAC (Base Realignment and Closure), July-August 2005 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - 18 H.R. Bills from the 110th Congress 1st and 2nd Session (envelope), 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Congressional orientation, December 1994 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1990s-2000s (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Townhouse (photographs), Circa 1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    Print outs of photographs also found on CDs in box 55.
  - Photographs of awards, plaques, and other photographs, 2000s (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Prince William County precinct map, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Plaques, certificates and flags (Box 54)
  - CDs (photographs); VHS, 2002-2007 (Box 55)
  - Book on Tobacco; Medicare constituent cards; Name plaque; Report on 14th St. Bridge Corridor Improvement Study, 1997-2001 (Box 56)
  - Plaques; Stamp, 1990s-2000s (Box 57)
  - Plaques and awards, 1990s-2000s (Box 58)
  - Plaques and awards, 1990s-2000s (Box 59)
  - Plaques and awards, 1990s-2000s (Box 60)